allstarhealth.com 2018-08-22

# AllStarHealth.com - Policies

## Frequently Asked Questions

**1.** Shipping Options

More than 98% of orders placed before 3PM local time ship the same business day. Almost all remaining orders ship the following day. You will receive an email from us if there is an unforeseen delay that may cause your order to arrive later than expected. Please note that all transit times are listed in business days. This excludes Saturdays, Sundays, and most holidays. If your shipment is late and you think there is a problem with the delivery, we encourage you to contact us via email. We will investigate the inquiry and respond in a prompt manner.

**_Within the Contiguous 48 States:_** Standard shipping is **just $5.95 per order;** regardless of how many items you wish to purchase. Please note that YOU MAY ONLY SELECT THE DOMESTIC STANDARD OPTION IF YOU ARE SHIPPING TO AN ADDRESS THAT CAN ACCEPT SHIPMENTS FROM BOTH UPS AND THE U.S. POSTAL SERVICE. Domestic Standard shipments may be delivered by either of the two carriers and we cannot determine which of the two will ultimately deliver the package. Occasionally, UPS will deliver the package to the local post office and the post office will then deliver it to your door. Transit time is typically 1-5 business days. You will be provided with a tracking number via email as soon as your order is shipped.

You may choose to upgrade your shipping to Next-Day, 2-Day, or 3-Day delivery once you are ready to check out. All transit times are listed in business days. The additional shipping charges for upgraded air shipments will be calculated based on the weight of the products you purchase and the proximity to our shipping facility. To select a different shipping option, you will need to type in your delivery zip code and scroll down to the desired shipping option. Please note that if you live outside of the contiguous 48 states you must select "USPS Priority Mail" as your delivery option.

**_Hawaii, Alaska, and US Territories:_** If you live in Alaska, Hawaii, or a U.S. territory, your order must be sent via USPS Priority Mail. YOU MUST SELECT USPS PRIORITY MAIL AS YOUR SHIPPING OPTION OR YOUR ORDER WILL NOT BE PROCESSED. USPS Priority Mail usually arrives within 2-4 days, however, it is not guaranteed and it cannot be tracked until it is delivered. While we do our best to accommodate our customers in these areas, we cannot offer our standard $5.95 domestic flat-rate for these orders. Your actual shipping charges depend on distance and weight of the order and will be calculated on the shopping cart page..

**_Military Addresses:_** If you are stationed at a military address overseas, your order must be sent via USPS Priority Mail. YOU MUST SELECT PRIORITY MAIL AS YOUR SHIPPING OPTION OR YOUR ORDER WILL NOT BE PROCESSED. Priority Mail to overseas military addresses usually arrives within 7-20 business days, however, it is not guaranteed and cannot always be tracked. Actual shipping charges will be calculated on the shopping cart page and depend on location and weight of the order. Since the US Postal Service does not offer package tracking for most military addresses, we cannot issue refunds on lost shipments unless they are returned to us.

**_P.O. Boxes:_** If your delivery address is a United States P.O. Box, your order will be sent via USPS Priority Mail. YOU MUST SELECT USPS PRIORITY MAIL AS YOUR SHIPPING OPTION OR YOUR ORDER WILL NOT BE PROCESSED. Priority Mail usually arrives within 1-3 business days. Actual shipping charges will be calculated on the shopping cart page and depend on distance and weight of the order. Please note that because UPS cannot deliver to P.O. boxes, shipping rates may be more expensive. Having your order sent to a place that accepts both UPS and US Postal Service is recommended if you wish to keep your shipping costs low.

**_International:_** Shipping charges for each carrier will be displayed on your cart page once you select a ship-to country. We are currently shipping only to select countries. If the country you would like the products shipped to is not listed, your best option is to have them shipped to a friend or relative within the United States that can forward the package to you once they receive it. A complete list of valid countries is available in the scroll box on the shopping cart page.

We will write the actual value of your order on the customs form attached to the box. Any customs, import duties, or additional taxes must be paid by the recipient. AllStarHealth.com has no control over these charges.

We encourage you to call your customs office to find out the exact import taxes or duties you will need to pay before you place your order. Please note that some nutritional supplements may not be allowed into your country. AllStarHealth.com will not issue refunds for orders that are denied entry through customs. You are responsible for checking the customs regulations in your country before placing your order.

Please note that our currently posted processing time does not apply for International orders. Because of special regulations that apply only to International orders, you may experience a 1-3 day delay in processing your order. If you are using a credit card that was issued by a foreign bank, you may be required to fax or email credit card documentation after your order is placed. Please understand that we ask for this documentation as a security measure to insure your credit card security. You will only be asked to provide this information on your initial order.

**2.** Refunds and Returns

If you are not satisfied with a product you purchased, you may return the unused portion for a full refund of the purchase price within 30 days of purchase. The unused portion must contain at least 25% of the original portion of the product. Unfortunately, we cannot refund the original and return shipping charges. If you were shipped the wrong product in error, you may return the product at our expense for a full refund of the purchase price and shipping charges. You must call 800-875-0448 to get a Return Merchandise Authorization number (RMA) prior to shipping your return. We reserve the right to refuse RMA's if our return policy is being abused.

If you purchase nutrition bars that contain chocolate, they may melt during transit. Although this problem is rare, we suggest that you refrigerate all chocolate products as soon as you receive them to restore consistency. WE DO NOT ACCEPT RETURNS ON MELTED PRODUCTS.

Our return policy is applicable to all products purchased at AllStarHealth.com with the exception of products manufactured by the following brands:

  * • Blistex
  * • Cellucor
  * • Corr-Jensen Labs
  * • Halo
  * • Hollywood Diet
  * • Jay Robb
  * • Kirkman
  * • Man Sports
  * • Nature's Best
  * • Promax
  * • Ultimate Nutrition
  * • Vital Earth Minerals
  * • Vitol

Unfortunately, the manufacturers listed above will not allow us to handle your return. If you purchased product from one of these manufacturers, you will need to contact them directly to arrange your return. The phone number and web address of the appropriate manufacturer should be listed near the UPC code on the product.

We do not accept open returns of any product within our fragrance category. If the fragrance is unused and in its original packaging, you may return it to us within 30 days of purchase.

To ensure delivery of your order, we have chosen reputable carriers for all of our domestic orders. All of our domestic shipments are sent with delivery confirmation from either the US Postal Service or UPS. AllStarHealth.com is not responsible for undamaged merchandise once delivery has been confirmed by UPS or the US Postal Service. All mail or parcels that are lost after delivery will be the sole responsibility of the consumer and all claims for packages lost after delivery will have to be filed directly with UPS or the US Postal Service. Parcels that are either refused by the recipient or returned to us due to an incorrect or undeliverable address will be processed as returns. You will receive a refund for the purchase price of your order minus the shipping charges.

**3.** Tracking an Order

When your order is placed, you will receive an email with your order receipt. The email will include a link that you can use to check the current status of your order. If the shipping method used has a tracking number, the link will be updated to include the tracking number for your order once the order has been shipped. You will also receive a second email with your tracking information attached when your order is shipped. Unfortunately, tracking is usually not available for FPO or APO military address and we will not be able to provide you with tracking information.

**4.** Payment Methods

We accept Visa, MasterCard, Discover, American Express and checks. Checks must be received within 30 days of order and will be held until cleared.

**5.** Security and Privacy

All Star Health is committed to your privacy. Uses of your information are limited to the ways outlined in this notice, except as required by law and/or to comply with a judicial proceeding, court order, or legal process served on our website. This Privacy Notice describes the following:

 _What kind of information about me do we collect?_ _What technology do we use when you visit our website?_ _How do we use the information that is collected?_ _How Do We Share Information?_ _What information can I access or modify? Can I opt-out?_ _How Do we Keep Information Secure?_

_What kind of information do we collect?_

We collect your contact information upon account set-up or at the time you place an order (such as name, shipping and email address, or phone number), username and password for the account, your credit or debit card information (including card number, cardholder name, expiration date, security code, and billing address). 

We also collect information on how you use our site, your purchase and return information, contact information for any friends you referred, copies of any emails that have been sent or received along with phone conversation notes, information you provide by interacting with us through reviews submitted to the site, social media (including photographs), shopping behavior and preferences, and other details that you may submit to us or that may be included in the information provided to us by third parties.

 _What technology do we use when you visit our website?_

When you visit our website or use our mobile applications, we may collect certain information by automated means, such as cookies, web beacons and other technologies. A cookie is a text file that website send to a visitor‘s computer or Internet-connected device to uniquely identify the visitor’s browser or to store information or settings in the browser. Cookies are a mechanism to remember information about you when you navigate from one web page to another. Our website uses cookies to hold a user's unique session identifiers, allowing us to serve correct information back to the user. This information includes your shopping cart items, or whether you are logged in. Our website cookies do not hold any personally identifiable information. All Star Health may use other similar technologies which allow us to collect non-personally identifiable information about your visit to help us better your experience. A web beacon, also known as an Internet tag, pixel tag or clear GIF, is used to transmit information back to a web server. We also may use third-party website analytics tools (such as Google), that collect information about visitor traffic on our site and mobile applications. The information we may collect includes information about the devices our visitors use to access the Internet such as IP address and the device, browser, operating system type and date/time stamp, clickstream data, URLs that refer visitors to our site, information on actions taken on our site such as page views and site navigation patterns, and a general geographic location (such as country and city) from which a visitor accesses our website, search terms that visitors use to reach our site.

We also may allow third-party companies to collect non-personally identifiable information when you visit the site and to use that information to serve ads for our products or services or for products or services of other companies when you visit the site or other website. These companies may use non-personally identifiable information (such as navigational, clickstream information, browser type, time and date, subject of advertisements clicked or scrolled over, etc.) during your visits to the site and other website in order to provide advertisements about our goods and services likely to be of interest to you. These parties may use a cookie or a third party web beacon, or other technologies, to collect this information.

When you use your mobile device we may receive non-personally identifiable information, such as a unique identifier for your device letting us know what type of phone you are using.

This information helps us customize your website experience and make our marketing messages more relevant. It also allows us to provide features such as saving your cart between visits. In order to provide the best customer experience possible, we also use this information for reporting and analysis purposes, such as how you are shopping our website, and performance of our marketing efforts.

_How do we use the information that is collected?_

All information we obtain is used to process, ship and provide customer service for your orders. After you place an order your contact information may be used to contact you regarding any issues or to get in touch with you regarding the status of your order. You will automatically receive refill reminder emails unless you opt-out at the time the order is placed by clicking the opt-out button, or by replying to customer service from the refill reminder e mail asking us to stop sending the emails. We never process orders without your consent, and do not participate in auto-fulfillment or subscription services for your account. Newsletters will be automatically sent unless you opt-out when placing your first order, or by emailing customerservice@allstarhealth.com to opt-out at any time. 

All Star Health utilizes third-party service providers to facilitate transactions and improve your experience. Examples of third-party service providers include credit card processing services, affiliate marketing, and email marketing providers. Any information that we share with a third-party service provider is done safely, securely, and under a contractual relationship with that provider to protect your data.

On our website, we may collect information about your online activities to provide advertising about products and services tailored to your individual interests. We also engage with third-party advertising networks. Ad networks may include third-party ad servers, ad technology vendors and research firms. We are not responsible for the privacy practices of these third parties, and we encourage you to read their privacy policies, which may apply to these third-party programs. Ad networks allow us to target our advertising to users through demographic, behavioral and contextual means. After you visit our website, these ad networks may continue to track your online activities over time across third-party website or online services by collecting information through automated means, including through the use of cookies, identifiers, web server logs, web beacons and other methods. Ad networks use this information to show you advertisements. The information our ad network vendors collect includes information about your visits to website that participate in the vendors’ advertising networks, such as the pages or advertisements you have viewed, and the actions you take on the site. This data collection and ad targeting take place both on our website and on third-party website that participate in the ad networks. This process also helps us track the effectiveness of our marketing efforts.

 _How Do We Share Information?_

We do not sell, share or otherwise disclose personal information about you, except as described in this Privacy Notice.

We may share the personal information we collect with our parent, affiliate and subsidiary companies, business partners, fulfillment center, ad network vendors and their participants, and other third parties for the purposes described in this Privacy Notice, and to communicate with you about products and services, offers, events and promotions. We also may share personal information with our service providers who perform services on our behalf. These service providers are not authorized by us to use or disclose the information except as necessary to perform services on our behalf or comply with legal requirements.

We also may disclose information about you to respond to judicial process and provide information to law enforcement agencies in accordance with applicable law, or when we believe disclosure is necessary or appropriate to prevent physical harm or financial loss or in connection with an investigation of suspected or actual illegal activity. We also reserve the right to transfer personal information we have about you in the event we sell, merge or transfer all or a portion of our business or assets. Following such a sale, merger or transfer of any kind, you may contact the entity to which we transferred your personal information with any inquiries concerning the processing of that information.

_What information can I access or modify? Can I opt-out?_

At any time you can adjust your preferences including opting out of newsletters or promotional emails, modifying or removing account information, or disabling your account. You may do this by calling or emailing customer service.

 ** _CONTACT INFORMATION_**  
Email : CustomerService@AllStarHealth.com  
Toll Free: 1-800-875-0448  
International: 001-714-698-0564  
Mon-Fri 6AM to 6PM Pacific Time

_How Do we Keep Information Secure?_

AllStarHealth.com uses SSL (secure socket layer) to encrypt information before it is sent across the internet. This can be verified by checking for the lock or key icon in the status bar of your browser. Sensitive information is stored in encrypted form according to Payment Card Industry Data Security Standards. If you do not feel comfortable sending your credit card information online, you may call us or fax the information to **714-891-8989**.

We maintain administrative, technical and physical safeguards designed to assist us in protecting the personal information we collect against accidental, unlawful or unauthorized destruction, loss, alteration, access, disclosure or use. We are confident of our security measures and will reimburse our customers for any fraudulent activity that may arise from use of a credit card at our site. Consumer protection laws limit consumer liability to $50 if the fraud is reported within 60 days. Almost all credit card companies waive the $50 charge. In the event that your card company does not waive these charges, we will reimburse you for the amount your card company charges you, up to the $50 legal maximum. To further protect yourself, you should safeguard your account user name and password, if any, and not share that information with anyone. Please contact us if you have any questions or require more information.

**6.** Low Price Guarantee

AllStarHealth.com will not be undersold. If you find a lower advertised price on your online order, please email or call us before placing your order and we will beat the price. Please be sure to take into account the total cost of the order, including shipping and handling.

Please keep in mind that the low-price guarantee applies to an identical order for a lower price. We will not mix and match prices from more than one store. AllStarHealth.com reserves the right to deny our low-price guarantee at our discretion. Our low-price guarantee applies to products listed on our web site that have not been discontinued by manufacturers. Our low-price guarantee does not apply to Clearance prices or short dated products. Competitor online items must be in stock at the time a price match is requested. Price matches can't be combined with other discounts or coupons.

**7.** Terms of Use

All logos, graphics, and text appearing on this web site is the "intellectual property" of AllStarHealth.com. The "intellectual property" is protected by laws governing the United States of America. Any reproduction or use of the "intellectual property" without the express written consent of AllStarHealth.com is prohibited.

AllStarHealth.com is not a manufacturer of nutrition products. This site is intended solely for the resale of nutritional supplements. All information provided on the web site is for informational purposes only and is not guaranteed to be correct. AllStarHealth.com will not be held liable for any problems that may arise from the consumption of the nutritional supplements sold on this web site. Placing an order at AllStarHealth.com signifies that you have read and agree to all of the policies listed on this policy page. Any and all legal issues pertaining to this web site shall be dealt with in the jurisdiction that AllStarHealth.com corresponds to.

By placing your order via this web site, telephone, fax, or email, you acknowledge that you have read and agree to all the policies listed on this page. By placing an order you also agree that these policies will serve as reference for any disputes that may arise regarding the contents or condition of your order. If you have any questions regarding our policies, please feel free to call us and one of our customer service representatives will assist you..

**8.** About Us

AllStarHealth.com was founded way back in the 20th century by two brothers working out of their Mom and Dad's one car garage. What we now believe was a sophisticated and covert plot by Mom and Dad to regain access to their rightful indoor parking spot, ultimately led the two of them to join their offspring in an effort to graduate from a startup home business experiment to a "real" company. Their hard work paid off just a few short months later when the garage got packed up and moved into the first of what would end up being 6 facilities over the course of the next 20+ years.

As is the case with most family owned businesses, it was an adventurous roller-coaster of a ride. The proverbial blood, sweat, and tears are to be expected when four family members and first-time business owners decide to take on the Goliath's of the industry like Amazon and GNC. But two decades later, the dream lives on. The previously mentioned 300 square foot garage has now grown to over 250,000 square feet of temperature controlled warehouse and office space with East and West Coast locations to insure your orders get to you quickly and efficiently no matter where in the world you call home. The initial 100 products that were available when the site was first launched has now grown to over 25,000 products from over 300 reputable manufacturers to insure you never have to look anywhere else to find what you need to keep you feeling healthy every day. And while the 4 family members and 3 initial employees still proudly call AllStarHealth.com their employer (all with slightly better titles than "order-packer" now), our proudest achievement has been the honor of growing our staff by providing well-paying, stable jobs to hundreds of families within our local community. We are still very much family owned and operated; the family just feels a whole lot bigger now.

We have never lost sight of how we got here… YOU! Without loyal customers like you, we would probably all go back to living in that house with the one car garage that started this all (if you’re wondering; Yes – Mom and Dad still live in that same house… and they got their parking spot back!). We will never forget how important it is to keep you happy, so we have made a commitment to offering you the best service and selection in the Industry. And most importantly, we are committed to keeping our prices low so that you don’t have to make compromises when it comes to your health. If you ever find a price lower than ours, tell us about it and we will beat it! We have real people, not machines, taking your phone calls. We answer emails 7 days per week. And needless to say, the web site is up 24/7. Whatever it takes, we are here to serve you. It's what we do!
